It's nothing personal.
Terminator 2: Judgment Day is a action, thriller, science
fiction film directed by James Cameron.
Ten years after the events of the original, a reprogrammed T-800 is sent back in
time to protect young John Connor from the shape-shifting T-1000.
Together with his mother Sarah, he fights to stop Skynet
from triggering a nuclear apocalypse.
The Terminator, played by Arnold Schwarzenegger.
Sarah Connor, played by Linda Hamilton.
John Connor, played by Edward Furlong.
T-1000, played by Robert Patrick.
Dr. Silberman, played by Earl Boen.
Miles Dyson, played by Joe Morton.
Starting in 1991, video games based on the Terminator film series have
been released throughout multiple console generations.
The films generally focus on humans attempting to prevent the
rise of Skynet, an artificial intelligence.
In the future, Skynet will wipe out most of humanity with
help from its army of Terminator machines.
The first Terminator game was released for DOS in July 1991, and is
based on the original film, The Terminator (1984).
Other games based on the first film and its sequel, Terminator 2:
Judgment Day (1991), were released over the next two years.
Subsequent films also received game adaptations, and several
non-film based games have also been released.
The film explores themes of man vs machine, cyborg,
shotgun, dystopia, moral ambiguity.
The tone is thought_provoking and intense.